<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<catalog>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>In this, the original book about the curious monkey, George is taken from the jungle by the man in the yellow hat to live in a new home, but--oh, what happened! Though trying to be good, George is still very curious and takes a swim in the ocean, escapes from jail, and goes for a flying ride on a bunch of balloons. This treasured classic is where it all began for the curious, loveable monkey and is a must have for any children's book collection.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/039515023X_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395150238&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George and the Birthday Surprise</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>When the man with the yellow hat tells George that he is planning a surprise, of course George is curious. Before long George finds a hat, noisemakers, decorations, and games. It must be a birthday! But whose birthday is it? That’s the surprise!</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618346872_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780618346875&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George and the Bunny</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Inspired by a vignette in the classic Curious George Flies a Kite, this is a sweet story of hide-and-seek.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395899222_lres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395899229&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George and the Firefighters</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>It’s the formula for success for preschoolers—Curious George and fire trucks! Curious George and the Firefighters is a story based on H. A. and Margret Rey’s popular primate and painted in the original watercolor and charcoal style. Firefighters are a famously brave lot, but can they withstand a visit from one curious monkey?</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/9780618494965_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780618494965&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George and the Puppies</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>When George and the man with the yellow hat visit the animal shelter, George is delighted to discover a large litter of puppies. At first, George just wants to pet the puppy, but then he wants to hold one. George's curiosity gets the best of him, and soon puppies are everywhere. </description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395912156_lres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395912157&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George and the Rocket</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>This lively story captures George’s adventure of becoming the first space monkey from the classic Curious George Gets a Medal.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618120696_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780618120697&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George at the Baseball Game</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Play ball! George is going to watch a baseball game. One curious little monkey in one big stadium makes for one exciting day at the ballpark!</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618663754_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780618663750&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Feeds the Animals</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>When a cuddly koala takes an interest in George's snack at the zoo, George is happy to share. In fact, George is happy to share with ALL the animals! Following a trail of peanuts, the zookeepers soon catch up with George and discover this little monkey is good for more than just mischief. </description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/039591910X_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395919101&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Flies a Kite</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>George's adventures with bunnies, fishing poles, and a powerful kite are told in a simplified text suitable for first-graders to read themselves.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395259371_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395259375&amp;srch=true#</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Gets a Medal</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>After repeatedly disastrous efforts to get himself out of trouble, George ends up being the first monkey in space.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395185599_lres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395185599&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Goes Camping</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Curious George Goes Camping is an entertaining story of the Great Outdoors based on H. A. and Margret Rey’s popular primate and painted in the original watercolor and charcoal style. George tries to be helpful, but he of course just ends up upsetting a nearby camper. As he’s hiding in the woods, he meets a forest creature who catapults the mischievous monkey into a chain of even more outrageous events!</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/9780395978351_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395978351&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Goes to a Chocolate Factory</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>When George and the man with the yellow hat stop to shop at a chocolate factory store, George becomes curious about how chocolates are made. Though he begins to follow the factory tour, George is soon off on his own to investigate. </description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395912148_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395912140&amp;srch=true#</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Goes to a Costume Party</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>George and the man with the yellow hat arrive at a Halloween party—but they aren’t wearing costumes. No matter—there are plenty in an old trunk upstairs, and soon George is trying on all kinds of outfits. But when he wants to look in the mirror, George finds he has to jump on the bed. Downstairs, the partygoers begin to hear noises. Then the lights go out and they hear a crash! Uh-oh. Did someone say the word ghost?</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618065695_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780618065691&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Goes to a Movie</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>The movie that George and the man with the yellow hat have been waiting to see is now playing! Once inside the darkened theater, George is curious about the light coming from the back of the room. As usual, George's curiosity gets him into trouble but his clever tricks save the day.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395919061_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395919064&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Goes to the Beach</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Curious George Goes to the Beach is a sunny summer story based on H. A. and Margret Rey’s popular primate and painted in the original watercolor and charcoal style. Once shore-side, Curious George plays ball, pretends to be a lifeguard, and discovers some very hungry seagulls! Can George help his friend Betsy overcome her fear of the ocean while saving the day? We all know the answer. Surf’s up!</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395978386_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395978382&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Goes to the Hospital</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>Readers learn all about the hospital as George goes in for an operation to remove a puzzle piece he has eaten.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395070627_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395070628&amp;srch=true#</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Goes to the Zoo</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>The zoo is the perfect place for a curious little monkey to make mischief and new friends! George is going to visit a new kind of zoo where the animals all roam free. Some of those animals look like a lot of fun—so much fun that a curious monkey can’t resist joining them. Giraffes and flamingos are close enough to touch, but George befriends a baby rhino who seems a little sad. Who better to lure her from her hiding place than George? And just in time for her special birthday party!</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/9780547315874_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547315874&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George in the Snow</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>George and the man with the yellow hat enjoy watching the winter sports competition. When they stop to warm up with some cocoa, George's curiosity about the racing equipment leads to some wild rides up and down the slopes. He creates quite a stir at the resort, and may even create a new sport! </description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/9780395919071_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395919071&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Learns the Alphabet</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Readers learn the alphabet along with George as the man in the yellow hat teaches the curious monkey how to read.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395137187_lres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395137185&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Makes Pancakes</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Every year George and the Man with the Yellow Hat attend the pancake breakfast to benefit the children’s hospital. Always curious, George finds his way to the pancake table. After making some of the most interesting pancakes the crowd has ever seen, George gets into even more monkey mischief. Activities include coloring, fun facts, and funny faces pancake recipe.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395919088_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395919088&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Rides a Bike</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>George helps a little boy with his paper route and gets into all sorts of trouble.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395174449_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395174449&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Takes a Train</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>Curious George heads to the train station to take a trip with the Man with the Yellow Hat, but when he tries to help out the station master, he gets himself into trouble. George finds himself a hiding place—only to discover that his help is really needed when a little boy’s toy train is about to fall onto the tracks. </description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/9780618065677_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780618065677&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Visits a Toy Store</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>A new toy store is opening and George can’t wait. Once George gets inside, the owner thinks his antics may be bad for business. It’s not long before George has her jumping through hoops to try to contain his curiosity. Will George’s playful nature really drive customers away, or will everyone’s favorite monkey find a clever way to save the day?</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618065709_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780618065707&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Visits the Zoo</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>Curious George and the man with the yellow hat visit the zoo. A hungry Curious George snatches a pail of bananas from the zoo keeper. Though he shouldn't have taken the bananas, George soon changes the zookeeper's shouts to praise with his clever, helpful ways.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395390303_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395390306&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George's ABCs</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Read from A to Z along with George in a condensed version of the classic Curious George Learns the Alphabet.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395899257_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780395899250&amp;srch=true#</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George's Dinosaur Discovery</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Curious George loves dinosaurs, so he’s excited to visit a dig to look for real dinosaur bones. Will the curious little monkey help make a big discovery?</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618663762_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547768588&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George's First Day of School</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>It’s the first day of school, and Curious George has been invited to Mr. Apple’s class to be a special helper! George is just the right monkey for the job—until he starts to wreak his usual havoc, that is. Red and yellow paint makes orange, yellow and blue makes green . . . and a mixture of all the paint colors makes a big mess! </description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618605649_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780618605644&amp;srch=true#</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>New Adventures of Curious George</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>H. A. Rey and his wife, Margret, first introduced young readers to the big-hearted, fun-loving troublemaker-hero Curious George in 1941. In this two-hundred-page hardcover treasury, Curious George fans will find eight stories based on the popular primate, painted in Rey’s original watercolor and charcoal style: Curious George Goes to a Chocolate Factory (1998), Curious George and the Puppies (1998), Curious George Makes Pancakes (1998), Curious George Feeds the Animals (1998), Curious George Goes to a Movie (1998), Curious George and the Hot Air Balloon (1998), Curious George in the Snow (1998), and Curious George’s Dream (1998). A five-page essay about the author-illustrator team closes this appealing collection of adventures for Curious George fans young and old.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618663738_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780618663736&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Treasury of Curious George</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>“He was a good little monkey and always very curious.” This is how H. A. Rey and his wife, Margret, first introduced their now beloved troublemaker-hero to young readers in 1941. In this hefty 192-page hardcover treasury, Curious George fans will find eight stories based on the popular primate, painted in Rey’s original watercolor and charcoal style: Curious George Takes a Train (2002), Curious George Visits a Toy Store (2002), Curious George and the Dump Truck (1999), Curious George and the Birthday Surprise (2003), Curious George Goes Camping (1999), Curious George Goes to a Costume Party (2001), Curious George Visits the Library (2003), and Curious George in the Big City (2001). A wonderful collection for your own mischievous monkey.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618538224_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780618538225&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
</catalog>