<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<catalog>
	
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Full Frame DVD</title>
		<description>Buckle up for this amusing, exciting and hilarious adventure with everyone's favorite inquisitive little monkey! When the Man in the Yellow Hat befriends Curious George in the jungle, they set off on a non-stop, fun-filled journey through the wonders of the big city and ultimately to the warmth of true friendship. Featuring the voice talents of Will Ferrell, Drew Barrymore and an all-star cast, Curious George is a family classic that will have the kid inside everyone giggling with delight again and again.</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-MHV61026160DVD-inhouse.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=481956458</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George 2 Follow That Monkey! DVD</title>
		<description>Join Curious George and The Man with the Yellow Hat as they set out on a madcap cross-country adventure to reunite Kayla, a homesick elephant, with her family. This unlikely trio faces all types of comic calamities and colorful characters and in the end learn that with family, friends and determination you can achieve anything.</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-00025195048736.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=499146309</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Zoo Night and Other Animal Stories DVD</title>
		<description>Join Curious George as he visits the zoo in this fun and educational animated series. H.A. Rey's classic book character jumps off the page and helps kids learn about math, science and engineering. Featuring narration by William H. Macy, this title features eight episodes of the popular PBS show.</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-MHV63020308-inhouse.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=481956460</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Goes to the Doctor and Lends a Helping Hand</title>
		<description>Curious George is curious about things happening all around him and sometimes he just has to try things for himself! Give your little one a chance to experience the fun in this captivating Curious George Goes to the Doctor and Lends a Helping Hand DVD.</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-MHV63102074DVD.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=481956461</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Sails with Pirates and Other Curious Capers DVD</title>
		<description>Everyone's favorite primate, Curious George, joins Hundley, Gnocchi, Bill and the Man in the Yellow Hat in eight fun-filled adventures spotlighting how exciting math, science and engineering can be. Bonus features include "George's Boat Game" and a DVD-ROM feature that lets you print out coloring pages and a connect-the-dots game. The Emmy-nominated series was a Parents' Choice 2008 Recommended Award Winner.</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-MHV63102076DVD-inhouse.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=481956462</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Makes New Friends DVD</title>
		<description>Tag along with everyone's favorite little monkey as he meets new friends in these 8 fun shows!</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-MHV63105688DVD-inhouse.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=481956465</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Goes Green DVD</title>
		<description>Everyone's favorite monkey has a brand-new mission: Save the Earth! George knows that it's easy when everybody lends a hand. Join George and his friends for eight, earth-friendly episodes as they grow their own gardens, learn about recycling and explore polar ice caps. With activities like these, you just can't miss Curious George Goes Green!</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-MHV63105689DVD-inhouse.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=481956466</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Robot Monkey and More Great Gadgets DVD</title>
		<description>George creates an awesome robot outfit that's so good it fools everyone, even The Man with the Yellow Hat and Professor Wiseman. Will George end up on display at the museum's new robot exhibit?</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-MHV63105690DVD-inhouse.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=481956467</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Back to School DVD</title>
		<description>Come along with George in 8 fun-filled episodes of his PBS KIDS® TV series as he discovers that you can learn new things at school, at home, and everywhere in between. Kids will be inspired to meet new friends at school after watching this Curious George Back to School DVD.</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-MHV63111764DVD.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=481956469</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George A Bike Ride Adventure DVD</title>
		<description>Get ready for adventure with everyone's favorite little monkey - Curious George! George is back with a whole lot of exciting things to do and learn in 8 more shows from his Daytime Emmy winning TV series. Join George as he goes on his first bike ride, chases rainbows, and meets canine royalty! Every day is a special day with Curious George: A Bike Ride Adventure!</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-MHV63115471DVD.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=477264934</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Very Monkey Christmas DVD (W/CD)</title>
		<description>Count down to Christmas with your favorite little monkey and The Man with the Yellow Hat! Follow along in this Curious George A Very Monkey Christmas DVD to see what they get each other for Christmas. The Man can't read George's wish list and George doesn't know what to get The Man with the Yellow Hat who seems to have everything!</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-MHV63116092DVD.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=495811590</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Plays Ball DVD</title>
		<description>Adventure awaits behind every corner in this Curious George Plays Ball DVD. Run the bases, and explore undergrounds tunnels with your favorite monkey from the children's TV series.</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-0025192077975.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=495751215</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Saves the Day DVD</title>
		<description>Join the mischievous monkey in this Curious George Saves the Day DVD for eight spectacular shows from the Emmy-winning PBS Kids series. Learn and laugh through the animated adventures.</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-9786314574031.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=495754946</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Takes a Job and More Monkey Business DVD</title>
		<description>This Curious George Takes a Job and More Monkey Business DVD features eight fun episodes that are narrated by actor William H. Macy. Children can follow along with George as he experiences working life at Chef Pisghetti's Ristorante. Together with Gnocchi the cat, the monkey tries out some extravagant recipes. George is as curious as ever in the full-length episodes and live-action segments contained in this spectacular compilation!</description>
		<prodimage>http://d3g6v733kz35fa.cloudfront.net/media/catalog/product/C/U/CUG-1110-MHV63100344DVD.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://www.shareasale.com/m-pr.cfm?merchantID=12990&amp;userID=667540&amp;productID=495754325</prodlink>
	</product>
</catalog>