<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<catalog>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George and the Puppies</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>When George and the man with the yellow hat visit the animal shelter, George is delighted to discover a large litter of puppies. At first, George just wants to pet the puppy, but then he wants to hold one. George's curiosity gets the best of him, and soon puppies are everywhere. </description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395912156_lres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547417073&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Makes Pancakes</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Every year, George and the man with the yellow hat attend a pancake breakfast to benefit the children’s hospital. Always curious, George finds his way to the pancake table and helps out. After making some of the most interesting pancakes the crowd has ever seen, George gets into even more monkey mischief!</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395919088_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547342078&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George and the Firefighters</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>It’s the formula for success for preschoolers—Curious George and fire trucks! Curious George and the Firefighters is a story based on H. A. and Margret Rey’s popular primate and painted in the original watercolor and charcoal style. Firefighters are a famously brave lot, but can they withstand a visit from one curious monkey?</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/9780618494965_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547342184&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>In this, the original book about the curious monkey, George is taken from the jungle by the man in the yellow hat to live in a new home, but--oh, what happened! Though trying to be good, George is still very curious and takes a swim in the ocean, escapes from jail, and goes for a flying ride on a bunch of balloons. This treasured classic is where it all began for the curious, loveable monkey and is a must have for any children's book collection.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/039515023X_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547416663&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George and the Hot Air Balloon</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>While on vacation, George and the man with the yellow hat stop to see Mt. Rushmore. There's no time to take a helicopter ride for a close-up view - the hot air balloon races are about to start! Whisked up and away at the races, a surprised George gets a close-up view of the presidents after all.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/9780547547459_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547342085&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Treasury of Curious George</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>“He was a good little monkey and always very curious.” This is how H. A. Rey and his wife, Margret, first introduced their now beloved troublemaker-hero to young readers in 1941. In this hefty 192-page hardcover treasury, Curious George fans will find eight stories based on the popular primate, painted in Rey’s original watercolor and charcoal style: Curious George Takes a Train (2002), Curious George Visits a Toy Store (2002), Curious George and the Dump Truck (1999), Curious George and the Birthday Surprise (2003), Curious George Goes Camping (1999), Curious George Goes to a Costume Party (2001), Curious George Visits the Library (2003), and Curious George in the Big City (2001). A wonderful collection for your own mischievous monkey.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618538224_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547347332&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>New Adventures of Curious George</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>H.A. Rey and his wife Margret first introduced young readers to the big-hearted, fun-loving troublemaker-hero Curious George in 1941. In this 200-page hardcover treasury, Curious George fans will find eight stories based on the popular primate, painted in Rey’s original watercolor and charcoal style: Curious George Goes to a Chocolate Factory (1998), Curious George and the Puppies (1998), Curious George Makes Pancakes (1998), Curious George Feeds the Animals (1998), Curious George Goes to a Movie (1998), Curious George and the Hot Air Balloon (1998), Curious George in the Snow (1998), and Curious George’s Dream (1998). A five-page essay about the author-illustrator team closes this appealing collection of adventures for Curious George fans young and old.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618663738_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547347448&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George's Dream</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>After a long day at the fair George is frustrated. It seems he is always too small! But when George falls asleep and wakes up BIG, he discovers being too large can be difficult, too, and maybe he's the right size after all.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395919118_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookRetail?isbn=9780547342047</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Flies a Kite</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>George's adventures with bunnies, fishing poles, and a powerful kite are told in a simplified text suitable for first-graders to read themselves.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395259371_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547342542&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Rides a Bike</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>George helps a little boy with his paper route and gets into all sorts of trouble.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395174449_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547342504&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Takes a Job</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Curious George runs away from the zoo and after many adventures ends up a movie star.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395186498_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547342528&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Learns to Count from 1 to 100</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Curious George is a good little monkey, and always very curious. Now George is curious about numbers. Counting from 1 to 10 is easy, but can he count all the way to 100? George has picked the perfect day to try. It’s his town’s 100th birthday today and everyone is coming out to celebrate!</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618476024_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547562865&amp;srch=true#</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Gets a Medal</title>
		<author>Rey/Rey</author>
		<description>After repeatedly disastrous efforts to get himself out of trouble, George ends up being the first monkey in space.</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0395185599_lres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547342511&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George at the Baseball Game</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Play ball! George is going to watch a baseball game. One curious little monkey in one big stadium makes for one exciting day at the ballpark!</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/0618663754_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547341798&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Plants a Tree</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>George loves to go to the science museum. So, when he finds out that the museum is planning a “Green Day” dedicated to recycling and planting trees, George is curious and wants to help out! But little monkeys eager to help can sometimes become little monkeys getting into trouble. When George begins to find and recycle things around town that aren’t quite ready for the recycle bin, he gets into a jam. Thankfully, George isn’t the only one who wants to help—the whole community can’t wait to lend a hand—and help George and the museum plant some trees!</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/9780547150871_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547416472&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
	<product>
		<title>Curious George Goes Camping</title>
		<author>Rey, H. A.</author>
		<description>Curious George Goes Camping is an entertaining story of the Great Outdoors based on H. A. and Margret Rey’s popular primate and painted in the original watercolor and charcoal style. George tries to be helpful, but he of course just ends up upsetting a nearby camper. As he’s hiding in the woods, he meets a forest creature who catapults the mischievous monkey into a chain of even more outrageous events!</description>
		<prodimage>http://www.houghtonmifflinbooks.com/assets/product/9780395978351_hres.jpg</prodimage>
		<prodlink>http://hmhbooks.com/hmh/site/hmhbooks/bookdetails?isbn=9780547342160&amp;srch=true</prodlink>
	</product>
</catalog>